hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
I guess the storm is
going to come soon...
Let's hurry and head back
to the curry shop.
Oh my.
That thunder right now...
came from the direction
of the Katabami Gold Mine...
Raiga's
Counterattack
B-Boss.
R-Ranmaru!
Hey, wake up, Ranmaru!
Quit joking around.
I'm not laughing...
Hey... Ranmaru...!
You... What did you do
to Ranmaru?
N-No! He...
When Ranmaru held your hand...
you revived and...
And then... Ranmaru...
Ranmaru...
Why is Raiga up?!
I must stop him.
Thunder?
Could it be?!
You're slow!
Are you... that brat's comrade...?
If it's a wooden weapon then...
But I can't hold it over my head...
You're annoying!
You little fly...!
Quit buzzing!
I'm... not smart you know...
Huh...?
I don't know why this happened...
Hey, whose fault is it? Yours?!
N-No! That's not true!
Perhaps... the guys from the Leaf...
Oh yeah...
If they didn't come
then Ranmaru and I would
have been together forever...
Where are they?!
You know don't you?!
If you don't know I'll kill you!
I know...
Maybe...!
Take me... where they are...
Go!
Yes!
Hold on, Ranmaru.
For your funeral...
I'll offer up their corpses for you.
Ranmaru...
This child... Did he give up his life
in order to revive Raiga?
Rai... ga... Rai...
Ranmaru! You're alive!
Hang in there! Ranmaru!
Ranmaru!
It started raining.
But we're almost done.
Oh my, I'm happy that
you all did this much for me.
Oh no!
Mom! Something horrible happened!
Oh my... What happened, Karashi?
Tenten is...!
What happened to Tenten?
She... fell from a cliff and..
What?!
What do you mean?!
I was running with her and
Tenten said that she would train me
in place of Lee...
But there... when we were
approaching the Lightning Pass
the lightning struck and
a tree came falling and
Tenten fell from the Pass
to the bottom of the cliff!
Oh my! Then you must go
help her out immediately!
Let's go to help Tenten!
Yeah!
Umm... No I will...
I will come after you guys
with the first-aid kit.
Okay.
Let's go Naruto, Lee.
— Yes!
— Right!
Oh my, Karashi?
Mom, we're running away
from here.
What are you saying, child?!
Never mind that!
I'll explain it later
so hurry up and get ready.
I will wait at the Lightning Pass.
Bring them for sure. If not...
I'll offer up you and your mom's corpses
to Ranmaru...
Mom, please!
I don't want to!
I'm going to wait
until everybody comes back!
Mom! You are so stubborn!
Just come with me!
Do you think that Tenten would
fall off a cliff
merely because of the thunder?
Huh? What do you mean?
That Karashi...
It seems like he wasn't trained enough.
I'm sorry...
Then...
Perhaps... it's some kind
of trap again.
Or he's been threatened
by someone...
But the Kurosuki Family is...!
Maybe my eyes were cloudy...
No way!
It's him...
He's burning up with fever...
Raiga...?
He revived so you should too...
It's all right. I'm going to die
soon anyway.
No way! I'm not going to let you say
that you're going to die so easily!
The people who were killed by you
and Raiga died against their will!
I'm not going to let it go your way!
For the sake of those
whose freedoms you took away.
I'm going to have you
take responsibility!
Are you okay?
The storm... It'll be dangerous
to stay here...
To Grandma's place.
You've come!
Raiga!
So he is alive.
This time I'll take you down for sure!
Let's go!
That's not good! Lee!
What are you...?
What is this?
It's on a whole different level
from before...!
Probably that attack was
lightning made of Chakra.
But this one...
Real lightning is used as the source...
If he can utilize the power of nature
unlike Chakra he'll have no limits!
Get down!
Byakugan!
If we dodge through
the electric shock and
take this to a close-range battle...
Naruto!
I know it!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Good job, Naruto!
Gentle Fist!
Neji!
You brats! Is that all you know?
Unlike the natural thunder power
I'm using
Chakra has its limits!
Huh...?
You're an idiot!
There's an idiot here!
Is that what you say to an opponent
who fought with all his power?!
Huh?
You again...
This time I'm not going to
have a funeral for you!
I am angry.
Oh my, what are you doing?!
Please Mom, come with me!
There's no time.
No, I'm going to stay here!
Oh, Tenten!
Oh my! This stupid son of mine!
I couldn't help it
because the boss came back to life...
If we stay here
we're going to get killed.
The only choice we have
is to run away!
If you want to run away
then go.
I'm not running away.
I'm not going to give up,
I will save this child.
I will feed this boy
the curry of life!
Grandma...
It's the curry that revived Lee.
Yes.
If anything happens
it's not my fault!
You!
One, two...
One, two... One, two...
This is bad...
This is really bad!
Eat this... you'll feel better.
Please.
You messed up on
mixing the spices.
Oh my?!
Karashi, could you have memorized
my recipe of the curry of life?
Karashi...
This is the true curry of life.
Here please eat this.
You can't even eat
if you're not with Raiga?
Why...?
Why... for a person like me?
Does one need a reason
to save someone?
To save you
Grandma Sansho and Karashi
did their best to make the curry.
Don't you feel anything seeing
those two trying their best?
If you don't feel anything
you're a horrible human being!
Human beings support each other
in order to live...
If there are people who need help
don't others naturally lend them a hand?
Isn't that being human?
Anyway, one bite is fine.
Why don't you try it?
Was it good?
That is what it feels like to live.
Raiga...
I want him to eat this curry too.
Let's go.
I'm far from finished...!
This guy...
What is up with him?
dokomademo tsudzuku michi ni wa ironna koto arunda ne
so many things happen on this endless road, right?
tsuyogari na kimi ga kyou wa juwaki koshi ni namida koe
although you're strong-willed your voice wavered on the phone today
donna yume oikakete kokomade kitan darou
what dreams did you chase to get here?
wakara na kunattari suru koto wa boku ni datte aru kara nee BABY
even I have times when I just don't understand baby
kimi ga namida no toki ni wa boku ga soba ni iru kara
when you're sad I'll be close to you
hanareba nare no yoru datte boku wa soba ni iru kara
even on nights when we're apart I'll be close to you
boku wa soba ni iru kara
I'll be close to you
Damn it! What in the world
happened to my body?!
It is pitch black in front of me,
my entire body is numb
and my body doesn't do
what I want it to do.
What is this feeling...?
It's warm, my entire body
is burning
and what is this taste that brings energy
up from the bottom of my stomach...?
Next time:
"Run!!! The Curry of Life."